Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Annex Files
1854, 1909, 1923-2014
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 39
248.25 Linear feet in 192 record cartons, 5 flat boxes, and 34 oversized boxes
The Time Inc. Annex Files is an assembled collection created by the archivists at Time Inc. of materials considered too bulky or infrequently requested to be housed in the main archives. Records in the Annex Files seem to be an extension of the of the materials in the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1) and document the history of Time Inc. as an organization with information on each publication and many departments at Time Inc. The collection is largely made up of records pertaining to the development of magazines, The March of Time, Home Box Office (HBO), Time-Life Books, and information on public affairs programs and events, international business, and advertising studies and surveys.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials may include contracts and consent forms. Restricted materials are located in boxes R40, R41, and R69-R85. Unreformatted audiovisual and digital material in the collection is not accessible. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically based on the original arrangement.
Historical Note
The Time Inc. Annex Files were assembled by the archivists at Time Inc. from materials considered too bulky or infrequently requested to be housed in the main archives. The archivists moved these records from the Time Inc. Archives' Library to a lower floor within the Time Inc. building to save space. The materials were housed in the building's sub-basement prior to the 2015 donation donated to the New-York Historical Society in 2015.
Citation: Hooper, Bill. Email to Holly Deakyne, 2016 June 10.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Materials
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Due to the nature of this collection described in the Historial Note many of the other record groups in the Time Inc. Records contain related materials.
Scope and Contents
The Time Inc. Annex Files seem to be an extension of the materials in the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1) documenting the history of Time Inc. as an organization and include information on each publication and many departments at Time Inc. The Subject Files were assembled for use by writers and researchers working on three authorized volumes of Time Inc. history, and the Annex Files were presumably not part of this project.
Departments and offices include but are not limited to: Time Inc.'s magazines such as Architectural Forum, Fortune, Life, People, Sports Illustrated, Time, and smaller titles; as well as Time-Life Books, Home Box Office (HBO), and Corporate Development; and The March of Time. Main topics include The March of Time newsreels and radio program; international business studies and agreements; marketing studies and surveys; records on public affairs programs and conferences; samples of non-Time Inc. publications for study, and "war task" information and propaganda material produced by Time Inc. in cooperation with the United States government during the Second World War for both civilian and military consumption. Specific items of interest include the scripts from The March of Time radio program, newsreels, and movie specials.
Advertising.; Advertising, Magazine; Advertising -- Periodicals; Continuities.; Corporation records.; Corporations -- History.; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Dope sheets.; Journalism -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Motion picture journalism; Newsreels; Organization files.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Radio journalism; Radio programs; Radio scripts; Reporters and reporting -- United States.; Screenplays.; Videocassettes.; March of time (Motion picture); March of time (Radio program); Time, inc. -- Archives.; Time, inc. -- History.
- Advertisers: Bulova, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 1)
- Advertisers: Chrysler, 1945-1948, 1962 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 2)
- Advertisers: General Electric, 1942-1949 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 3)
- Advertisers: Gulf, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 4)
- Advertisers: Miscellaneous, 1927, 1939-1963, 1970 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 5-6)
- Advertisers: RCA, 1949-1958 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 7)
- Advertisers: Sears Roebuck, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 8)
- Advertising: Barnes Agency Recognition, 1946-1947, 1955-1964 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 9)
- Advertising: Barnes War Contracts, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 10)
- Advertising: Corporate Campaigns, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 11)
- Advertising: 2005/05 McKinsey Strategic Analysis 2004-05 (Offsite-box 4009, Folder 1)
- Advertising: 2006 Strategy and Process Review (Offsite-box 4009, Folder 2)
- Advertising: 2010 Business Development Top Advertising Prospects (Offsite-box 4009, Folder 3)
- American Television and Communications Corporation, 1984, undated (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 12)
- Andrew Heiksell/Mayor Lindsay – WNEW TV (NY) Oct. 6, 1968 (Offsite-box 4007, Folder 1)
- Architectural Forum: Ads, 1929-1940, 1946 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 13)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Merchandising, 1937-1942 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 14)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Miscellaneous, 1935-1945, 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 15)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Promotion, 1925-1929, undated (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 16)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Promotion 9/31-3/32, 1931, undated (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 17)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Promotion Miscellaneous, 1933-1945, 1950, undated (Offsite-box 3849, Folder 18)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Promotion: Miscellaneous, 1933-1942, 1950, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 1-3)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Promotion: Miscellaneous, 1934-1942, 1954, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 4-5)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Rates, 1932-1949, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 6)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Promotion, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 7)
- Architectural Forum: Advertising: Promotion: Samples, 1933-1936 (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 8)
- Architectural Forum: Awards, 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 9)
- Architectural Forum: Budget, 1935-1941, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 10)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Annual, 1940, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 11)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Index, 1939, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 12)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Inquiries, 1937-1941 (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 13)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Issues 1937-1939 (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 14-15)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Issues 1940-1942 (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 16-17)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Newsletter, 1938-1941, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 18)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Promotion, 1937-1941, undated (Offsite-box 3850, Folder 19)
- Architectural Forum: Building Reporter: Miscellaneous, 1937-1945, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 1)
- Architectural Forum: Circulation, 1932-1954, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 2)
- Architectural Forum: Mailings: Prospect, 1934-1941, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 3)
- Architectural Forum: Circulation: Mailings: Renewall, 1934-1937 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 4)
- Architectural Forum: Circulation: Promotion: Samples, 1933-1937, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 5)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Analysis, 1934, 1941-1947, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 6)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Design Decade, 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 7)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: International, 1941-1942, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 8)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Issue Promotion, 1930-1940, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 9)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Main Street, USA, 1938, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 10)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Plus, 1938-1939 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 11)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Special Issues, 1933-1935 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 12)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: World's Fair, 1939 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 13)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Miscellaneous, 1936-1942, 1948, 1956-1958, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 14)
- Architectural Forum: Edit: Financial, 1941 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 15)
- Architectural Forum: History, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 16)
- Architectural Forum: Meetings and Round Table, 1944 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 17)
- Architectural Forum: Name Change to The Magazine of Building, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 1)
- Architectural Forum: Organization, 1940-1941, undated (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 18)
- Architectural Forum: Organization [RESTRICTED], 1941 (Offsite-box R69)
- Architectural Forum: Post-War, 1943 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 19)
- Architectural Forum: Pre-Fabrication, 1943 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 20)
- Architectural Forum: Pre-Time Inc.: Promotion: Samples, 1919-1931 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 21-23)
- Architectural Forum: Production, 1940, 1947 (Offsite-box 3851, Folder 24)
- Architectural Forum: Production [RESTRICTED], 1941 (Offsite-box R69)
- Architectural Forum: Promotion and Publicity: Issues 1933-1942 (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 1-2)
- Architectural Forum: Promotion and Publicity: Samples, 1929-1943, undated (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 3)
- Architectural Forum: Prospectus, 1932-1939 (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 4)
- Architectural Forum: Public Relations, 1934-1938, 1940, 1946, 1954 (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 5-6)
- Architectural Forum: Publicity, 1933-1944, undated (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 7)
- Architectural Forum: Purchase, 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 8)
- Architectural Forum: Purchase [RESTRICTED], 1932-1933 (Offsite-box R69)
- Architectural Forum: Record Merger, 1941, undated (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 9)
- Architectural Forum: Service Department, 1925-1928, undated (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 10)
- Architectural Forum: Single Issues: Samples, 1936 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 2)
- Architectural Forum: Skyline, undated (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 11)
- Architectural Forum: Special Issues: A Century of Progress Exposition, 1933 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 3)
- Architectural Forum: Special Issues: Boston, 1964 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 4)
- Architectural Forum: Special Issues: Chicago, 1962 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 5)
- Architectural Forum: Special Issues: Frank Lloyd-Wright, 1948 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 6)
- Architectural Forum: Special Issues: International Inserts, undated (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 7)
- Architectural Forum: Special Issues: World's Fair New York, 1939 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 8)
- Architectural Forum: Split House and Home/Architectural Forum, 1952 (Offsite-box 4011, Folder 9)
- Architectural Forum: Surveys: Five Star Home, 1936 (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 12)
- Architectural Forum: Surveys: Readership Preferences, 1925-1934, 1940-1944, undated (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 13)
- Architectural Forum: Surveys: Miscellaneous I, 1939-1945 (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 13-15)
- Architectural Forum: Surveys: Miscellaneous II, 1931-1939 (Offsite-box 3852, Folder 16-18)
- Architectural Forum: Surveys: Miscellaneous II, 1931-1939 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 1)
- Audit Bureau of Circulations (ABC): Circulation Statements, 1935-1953 (Offsite-box 4081)
  Scope and Contents
  Microfiche films.
- Audit Bureau of Circulations (ABC): Circulation Statememts, 1942 (Offsite-box 4082)
- Audit Bureau of Circulations (ABC): Circulation Statements, 1954-1973 (Offsite-box 4082)
- Audit Bureau of Circulations (ABC): Circulation Statements, 1968 (Offsite-box 4082)
- Board of Directors 1979 Operations Report (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors 1980 Operations Report (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 3)
- Bob Elson on Mike Wallace at Large, 1973 (Offsite-box 4007, Folder 2)
  Includes audiovisual material.
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Bob Elson on "Mike Wallace at Large" Air Date 5/24/73"
- Broadcast, undated (Offsite-box 4012, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting: Miscellaneous 1960 and Later, 1960-64 (Offsite-box 4012, Folder 2-3)
- Broadcasting: Political Coverage, 1949 (Offsite-box 4012, Folder 4)
- Christmas: Miscellaneous, 1958-1964 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 4)
- Cartoons, 1962, undated (Offsite-box 4012, Folder 5)
- Churchill, Winston: Memoirs Promotion, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 4012, Folder 6)
- Churchill, Winston: Miscellaneous, 1946, 1948, 1965 (Offsite-box 4012, Folder 7)
- Circulation: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC), 1932-1963 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 5)
- Circulation: Audit Bureau of Circulation (ABC), 1937, 1957 (Offsite-box 4042, Folder 1)
- Circulation: Agency Miscellaneous, 1926-1931, 1943-1956 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 6)
- Circulation: Agency Promotion, 1927-1934 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 7)
- Circulation: Agency Two-Pay, 1931-1939, 1945, undated (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 8)
- Circulation: Christmas: Cage Receipts and Volume Analyses, 1943-1949 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 9)
- Circulation: Christmas: Cage Receipts and Volume Analysis, 1949-1950, 1957 (Offsite-box 4042, Folder 2-4)
- Circulation: Christmas: Miscellaneous, 1942-1953 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 10)
- Circulation: Complaints, 1927, 1943-1950 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 11)
- Circulation: Corporate, 1937-1951, 1970, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 12-13)
- Circulation: Corporate, 1946 (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 11)
- Circulation: Corporate: Education Department, 1942-1957, 1986, undated (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 14)
- Circulation: Corporate: 1957 Greeting Card Test (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 15)
- Circulation: Distribution Studies, 1943-1951 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 16)
- Circulation: Duplication, 1938-1939, 1946-1952 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 17)
- Circulation: Expires, 1932-1943 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 18)
- Circulation: List Research, 1949-1954 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 19)
- Circulation: Military: Mailings, 1941-1953, undated (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 20-21)
- Circulation: Military: Miscellaneous, 1945-1947, 1965 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 22)
- Circulation: Newsstand, 1959-1964, undated (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 23-24)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Fortune: Coupon Test and Price Rest, 1951-1955 (Offsite-box 3853, Folder 25)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Life, 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 1)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Life: Coming to Life, 1936 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 2)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Life: Extended Sale Program, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 3-4)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Life: Market Research, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 5)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Life: Strictly Confidential, 1937, undated (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 6)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Life: Miscellaneous, 1936-1945, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 7)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Life: Canada, 1970 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 8)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 9)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Price Test, 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 10)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Price Test and Price Changes, 1955-1967 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 11-12)
- Circulation Newsstand: Price Test and Price Changes, undated (Offsite-box 4042, Folder 6)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Representatives' Publicity Activities, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 13)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Showcase Accounts: Retail Display Program (RDP): Contracts and Correspondence, 1954-1962 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 14)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Showcase Accounts: Retail Display Program (RDP): Contracts and Correspondence [RESTRICTED, 1956-1961 (Offsite-box R69)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Time: Election Extra 1960 and 1954, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 15)
- Circulation: Newsstand: Convention, 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 16)
- Circulation: Presentations, 1946-1948 (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 17)
- Circulation: Promotion, 1933-1951, undated (Offsite-box 3854, Folder 18)
- Circulation: Reporting Statistical, 1946-1948 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 1)
- Circulation: Time: International Mailings, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 2-3)
- Circulation: Transportation Copies, 1927-1934, 1946-1948 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 4)
- Circulation: Western Union, 1932-1934, 1947, undated (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 5)
- College Thesis, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 6)
- College Thesis, 1964 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 7)
- College Thesis, 1979 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 8)
- Company Services: Aircraft, 1945 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 9)
- Company Services: Communications, 1927, 1937-1963 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 10)
- Company Services: Distribution, 1934-1956, 1960, undated (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 11)
- Company Services: Space, 1937-1952 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 12-13)
- Company Services Space [RESTRICTED], 1937 (Offsite-box R69)
- Company Services: Telephone, 1937-1950, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 14)
- Company Services: Travel, 1941-1954 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 15)
- Company Services: Miscellaneous, 1937, 1943-1960 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 16)
- Corporate Affairs: Art Shows, 1956-1966 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 17)
- Corporate Affairs: Board of Directors Dinner, 1970 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 18)
- Corporate Affairs: Country Fairs, 1942-1947 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 19)
- Corporate Affairs: Dramatic Performances, 1954-1961, undated (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 20)
- Corporate Affairs: Grundwald/Cave Dinner, 1977 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 21)
- Corporate Affairs: Luce-Donovan Dinner, 1964, undated (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 22-23)
- Corporate Affairs: Time Inc.: Creative Conference Bermuda, 1977 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 24)
- Corporate Affairs: Time: Publishing Staff Summer Outing Poster, 1992 (Offsite-box 4042, Folder 5)
- Corporate Affairs: Time Inc.: Press Release, 1987 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 25)
- Corporate Affairs: Time Inc. Second Creative Conference June 18-21, 1978 (Offsite-box 4012, Folder 8)
- Corporate Affairs: Time Out, Chicago, 1941, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 26)
- Corporate Affairs: Time Out, New York, 1941, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 27-28)
- Corporate Affairs: Time Out, New York, 1950-1957 (Offsite-box 3855, Folder 29)
- Corporate Affairs: Time Out, New York 1950, 1950-1957 (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 1)
- Corporate Development: 1947-1952: Cinerama (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 2-4)
- Corporate Development: 1947-1952: Cinerama [RESTRICTED], 1947-1949 (Offsite-box R69)
- Corporate Development: 1952: Press Wireless, 1947-1955, 1962, 1965, undated (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 5)
- Corporate Development: 1953: Regional Newspaper Experiment, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 6)
- Corporate Development: 1958: Encyclopedia of American Industry, 1955-1958, undated (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 7)
- Corporate Development: 1961: Fortune Book Club (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 8)
- Corporate Development: 1961: American Express Vacation Club, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 9-10)
- Corporate Development: 1961: Longsmans, Green and Company (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 11)
- Corporate Development: 1961: Prentice-Hall (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 12)
- Corporate Development: 1961: Realities (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 13)
- Corporate Development: 1961 and Later: Itek, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 14)
- Corporate Development: 1962 and Before: Encyclopedia Folder #1, 1958-1962 (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 15-16)
- Corporate Development: 1962 and Before: Encyclopedia Folder #2 (Offsite-box 3856, Folder 17-18)
- Corporate Development: 1962: Almanac, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 1)
- Corporate Development: 1962: Education (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 2)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Education (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 3)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Education: Silberman, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 4)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Encyclopedia Folder #1 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 5-7)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Encyclopedia Folder #2 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 8-10)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Main Currents in American Society (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 11)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Pay Television (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 12)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Role of Mass Magazine in the U.S. by Austell and Grundwald (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 13)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Spindletop Survey of Mass Communications, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 14)
- Corporate Development: 1963: Television (Final Report) by Henry Grunwald, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 15)
- Corporate Development: 1963 and Later: British Telemeter (Pay Television), 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 16)
- Corporate Development: 1963-65: Magazine and Television Market Research, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 17)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Communications Satellite Corporation (COMSAT) (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 18)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: Adult (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 19)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: Audio-Visual, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 20)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: College Book Publishing, 1964, 1971 (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 21)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: College Book Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: Early Learning (Offsite-box 3857, Folder 22)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: Initial Teaching Alphabets (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 1)
- Corporate Development: 1964: International Correspondence Schools (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 2)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: Silberman Report: Appendices, undated (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 3)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: Silberman Report: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 4-5)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Education: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 6-7)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Electronic Encyclopedia, 1964, undated (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 8)
- Corporate Development: 1964: National Football League (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 9)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Norcross (Greeting Cards) (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 10)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Pay Television (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 11)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Spindletop Survey of Mass Communications (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 12-13)
- Corporate Development: 1964: Ultra High Frequency (UHF) (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 14)
- Corporate Development; 1964 and Later: Metro-Goldwyn-Meyer (MGM), 1964-1974 (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 15)
- Corporate Development: 1964-1965: Education Famous Artists School (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 16)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Cenco Instruments (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 17)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Corplan (ITT Study of Television), undated (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 18)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Diner's Club (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 19)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Eastman Kodak (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 20)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Education: Audio-Visual Study (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 21)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Education: Cambridge, 1964-1965, undated (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 22)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Education: Early Learning (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 23)
- Corporate Development: 1965: Education: Educational Testing Services, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 24)
- Corporate Development: 1965; Education: Markets Abroad (Preliminary Study), 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 25)
- Corporate Development: 1965; Education: Markets Abroad (Final) (Offsite-box 3858, Folder 26)